<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>CloverThemeManager Changelog</title>
        <link>http://sourceforge.net/p/cloverefiboot/themes/ci/master/tree/CloverThemeManagerApp/Updates/CTM_AppCast.xml?format=raw</link>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version <!--INSERT_BUILD_SHORT--></title>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.7.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head> 
    <link href='http://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Roboto+Condensed:400,300,700' rel='stylesheet' type='text/css'>
    <style>

html, body {
    background: #2d313a !important;
    height: 100%;
    margin: 0;
    padding: 0;
}
p {
    text-align: left;
    font-family: 'Roboto Condensed', sans-serif;
    margin-left: 60px;
    margin-right: 40px;
}
.textTitleHeading {
    color: #d1f4fb;
    font-size: 24px;
    font-weight: 400;
    line-height: 2px;
    margin-top: 46px;
}
.textTitleHeadingSml{
    color: #d1f4fb;
    font-size: 20px;
    font-weight: 400;
    line-height: 1px;
    margin-top: 120px;
    margin-bottom: 30px;
}
.textTitleSubLatestHeading {
    color: #d1f4fb;
    font-size: 16px;
    font-weight: 400;
    line-height: 120%;
}
.textTitleSubHeading {
    color: #d1f4fb;
    font-size: 13px;
    font-weight: 400;
    line-height: 120%;
}
.textSectionLatestBody {
    color: #98e5ea;
    font-size: 14px;
    line-height: 140%;
    font-weight: 300;
}
.textSectionBody {
    color: #98e5ea;
    font-size: 12px;
    line-height: 140%;
    font-weight: 300;
}
.band1 {
   border-top: 2px solid #3e434b;
    padding: 20px 0px 20px 0px;
}
.band2 {
    background: #292D36 none repeat scroll 0 0;
    border-top: 2px solid #3e434c;
    padding: 20px 0px 20px 0px;
}
a:link, a:visited {
    color: #BBB;
    text-decoration: none;
}
a:hover {
    color: #FFF;
}

    </style>

</head>
<body>
<a name="Top"></a>
<div id="Container">

        <div id="SpacerTop">&nbsp;</div>

        <p class="textTitleHeading">Latest version changelog</p>
        
        <!--<div class="band1">-->
          <p class="textTitleSubLatestHeading"><!--INSERT_BUILD_SHORT--></p>
          <p class="textSectionLatestBody">

- Identify fast boot and textonly boot modes from bootlog.<br>
- Simplify control options band for changing themes.<br>
- Extend keyboard support to identify Command key.<br>
- Return key now closes dialog boxes.<br>

          </p>
        <!--</div>-->

        <p class="textTitleHeadingSml">Changelog history</p>
        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.5</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Reduced height of bands when no thumbnail is shown.<br>
- Left and right arrow now changes view sizes from no thumbnail to expanded previews.<br>
- AlphaNumeric keypress will scroll UI to first Theme beginning with that character.<br>
- Removed out of date md5 check for determining original 80.save_nvram_plist.local.<br>
- TAB to select different interface controls.<br>
- Fix bug showing choice of embedded theme in bootlog section.<br>
- Added Update All button.<br>
- Fixed issue where a locally installed theme that had since been deleted from repo would be flagged with an available update.<br>
- Add tooltips to UI.<br>
- Added button to rescan selected partition.<br>
- Fixed multiple tick issue for ReadPrefs on Init screen.<br>
- Extend detection of repository.<br>
- Shorten length of time older index.gits are fetched.<br>
- Improve layout of set theme section.</p>

        <div class="band1">   
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.4</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Amend check for network connection.<br>
- Update detection for Clover revision.<br>
- Change text of ShowHideToggleButton button from Hide UnInstalled to Show Installed.<br>
- Increase speed of showing/hiding bootlog region.<br>
- Increase speed of showing/hiding accordion.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band2">   
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.3</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Integrated <a href="https://sparkle-project.org" target="_blank">Sparkle</a> framework for handling updates (Credit Micky1979).<br>
- Removed previous update code.<br>
- updateID no longer used.<br>
- Message box link colour changed to lighter blue.<br>
- bootlog trim action changed to better handle large data.<br>
- Workaround issue where additional update buttons could appear for themes with spaces in their name when toggling show all view.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">   
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.2</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Added a new user selectable feature to clean items downloaded to the App Support dir which may cause issue with loading the app if things have changed server-side, or the user is upgrading from an older version. (Credit to Micky1979 for his objective-c skills).<br>
- The main app now cleans the temporary dir rather than the bash script.<br>
- Fixed positioning issue with theme update check progress bar when bootlog is visible.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band2">
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.1 (updateID 16)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Click theme bands rather than image thumbnail to reveal large theme screenshot.<br>
- Fix bug where uninstalling a theme with an update still showed the update available.<br>
- Double check temp directory is removed at close of app.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.1 (updateID 15)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix two incorrect calls to the wrong git binary. <br>
- Change detection of default gateway dependent on use of either discoveryd or mDNSResponder.<br>
- Improve feedback on first page when loading the app.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.1 (updateID 14)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix issue where some actions would fail when running app from a path with spaces.<br>
- Fix issue detecting MBR boot device (thanks droples).</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.1</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- App can now be run from a read-only volume.<br>
- Script updates can only be performed when app is not on a read-only volume.<br>
- Insert line breaks in to injected html for easier reading.<br>
- Text on loading page, and bootlog info is now non-selectable.<br>
- Debug log mode is now set to off (enable if you experience problems).<br>
- Theme entries in nvram and config.plist are only checked when boot device is selected.<br>
- Removed unused growl framework to reduce app footprint.
- Updated credits.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0 (updateID 13)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Check for theme updates after using rescan option (Thanks droples).<br>
- Add 'Connecting to repository' status on loading page.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0 (updateID 12)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Test for non existent path after user cancelling rescan option (Thanks droples).<br>
- Fix shadows on update bands when UI is set to hide uninstalled themes.<br>
- Fix subsequent updates being removed after the first update when UI is set to hide uninstalled themes.<br>
- Only add an update button to the DOM if not already added.<br>
- Restore previous working directory after updating a theme.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0 (update 11) </p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix updating cloverthememanager.js.</p>
        </div>


        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0 (updateID 10)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fixed problem introduced with recent developments with the UI's handling of theme updates.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0 (update 9) </p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Change network detection.<br>
- Fix cancelling 'Mount ESP' operation.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.76.0</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Detect boot device on launch.<br>
- Read bootlog to learn what Clover finds on the users system for themes.<br>
- Add a collapsable area at the top of the UI for bootlog information. <br>
- Add theme control options to the bottom of the UI.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.9 beta5</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Resolve full path to EFI/Clover directory when Clover is installed on current volume.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.9 beta4</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Match case before checking for MBR boot sector signature.<br>
- Fix notification code injection for OS X versions newer than Lion.<br>
- Remove rogue character in script.sh.<br>
- Change network discovery for OS X Lion as netstat -r takes a while to complete.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.9 beta3</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Take active partition marker in to account when reading fdisk result.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.9 beta2</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- check UI theme control options exists before trying to hide/show them.<br>
- correct log message for identified MBR devices.<br>
- added more debugging statements to function FindMbrDevice().<br>
- adjust text size and positioning of theme control options to accommodate longer path.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.9 beta1</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- At launch, Clovers bootlog is read and an attempt is made to determine the boot device and mount it.<br>
- If a Clover bootlog is found then the relevant theme information is extracted and displayed in a collapsible area at the head of the main UI with the summary of what happened shown in the bootlog title bar.<br>
- When the boot device is selected, different options are presented for setting the next theme to use for boot, depending on the boot type (Legacy or UEFI).</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.6 (update 8)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Notifications are now not sent when running under 10.7<br>
- snabbt js library is no longer used. Bounce effect re-worked to work in 10.7 upwards.<br>
- Fix update for OS X 10.7.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.6 (update 7)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Updated jQuery to v2.1.3.<br>
- App update now prevents theme updates from running until user decides what to do.<br>
- Added notifications.<br>
- Update about window.<br>
- Add bounce effect to message box.<br>
- Enhance update routine to check for main app framework version change.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.5</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- add_themes help page is now loaded in default web browser rather than the Clover Theme Manager window.<br>
- add_themes help file tweaked.<br>
- Text for untracked themes dialog box updated with new description.<br>
- Untracked theme indicator changed from a cross to a question mark.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.4</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix issue Low Space warning message being accidentally fired.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.3</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix a couple of issues when returning from help page (Thanks droples).<br>
- Free space is no longer checked for when no partition is selected.<br>
- Order of some items sent to UI reverted to retain previous settings.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.2</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Remember user choice for enabled/disabled snow.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.1</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Enabled 'Open Log' menu item from CloverThemeManager menu.<br>
- Revise check for out-of-date index.git (due to re-built repo).<br>
- Activate SecurityAgent when running osascript on OS X 10.9 and newer in attempt to give dialog box the focus. The dialog box is correctly given the focus on OS X 10.7 but not later versions. Activating SecurityAgent in Yosemite seems to work on subsequent opening, just not the initial opening). Not sure how to do this in 10.9.<br>
- Switch to using JrC's partutil program for gathering disk and partition information.<br>
- Add option to disable/enable snow effect (will remove snow after winter).<br>
- Style nvram dropdown menu.<br>
- Add hover to message box close button.<br>
- Adjust vertical position of theme title when thumbnails are hidden.<br>
- Various code cleanups and bug fixes</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.0 (update 6)  </p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Theme update improvements.<br>
- Themes installed from the repo now have the last commit hash for that theme stored in a file named .hash in the theme directory. This hash is then used for checking against the hash in the repo for updates.<br>
- Changed to using unique partition GUID rather than volume UUID.<br>
- Installed themes are only recorded in prefs if partition has a unique GUID.<br>
- Fix bug where help file was deleted.<br>
- Fix bug where volume dropdown menu wasn't re-populated when returning from help page.<br>
- Tested on 10.7, 10.8, 10.9 and 10.10 </p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.75.0 (update 4)</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Added some Christmas fun by the way of the BSD licensed snowstorm</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.??.?? - 9th December 2014</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Revise disk reading routine and put in to separate script to allow multithreading.<br>
- Revise ESP routines.<br>
- Improve feedback on initialisation page.<br>
- Volume drop down menu now populated by javascript.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.??.?? - 10th December 2014</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- App update procedure is now separate from index.git.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.??.??</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Add version numbers to other scripts and show on initialisation page.<br>
- Check for app updates later in the launch process, just before showing the UI.<br>
- UI now correctly enables when selecting 'No' to app updates dialog.<br>
- Full path to EFI/Clover/Themes now shown for ESP in volume dropdown menu.<br>
- Don't remove volume dropdown menu title if selected volume no longer exists.<br>
- Clover.Theme nvram var is now checked against installed themes for ESP (thanks droplets).<br>
- Free space text is now shown for ESP after mounting.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.74.2</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Enable mounting and working with EFI System Partition(s).</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.74</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Implement remote updating of the app/public directory (the inner scripts) at users choice.<br>
- Add check for any themes in your theme directory that do not match themes in the repo.<br>
- Improved git detection.
- Changed app name in menu.
- Apply font style to theme list</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.73</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Add showing/hiding previews for update theme bands.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.72</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- UI theme dir dropdown list now used values of array ID.<br>
- Record and use mount points from diskutil info -plist.<br>
- Handle spaces in mount points.<br>
- Assign zero'd volume UUID for MBR partitioned devices.<br>
- Send update list to UI even if no path selected to enable interface.<br>
- Add debug info to log for $PATH and result of which command.<br>
- Fix bug where incorrect theme would be removed from prefs.<br>
- Various code clean ups.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.71</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Don't housekeep prefs and theme.gits for Volumes that are no longer mounted - For example, an unmounted ESP.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.70</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Check for local installation of git and display installation instructions if not found.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.69</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix bug when reading empty pref entries for last selected volume and path.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.61</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Add a secondary overlay, rather than use the same one as used for the message boxes, to prevent user interaction when checking for updated theme list and updates from the repo.<br>
- Relayout some of the UI elements.<br>
- Implement accepting user password to allow changes that require root privileges.<br>
- The app can now set Clover. Theme nvram variable.<br>
- Fix bug where multiple updates weren't detected on a secondary scan.<br>
- Implemented slimmer view option to see more themes at once.<br>
- Can perform [Read: basic]  install from the command line. </p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.60</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix javascript bug where update buttons did not have eventlisteners.<br>
- Fix a couple of css errors.<br>
- Improve javascript message log reading.<br>
- Changed method for checking svn status.<br>
- Add 'U' indicator beside theme control button for themes not under version control.<br>
- Add available free space for selected path to UI.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.59</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Check for local installation of git and display installation instructions if not found.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.58</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Fix symbolic link to images directory.<br>
- Hide open path button, if no paths are available.<br>
- Update mechanism is now functioning well (apart from known bug mentioned below).<br>
- Make UI theme band colours stronger. Update band is now blue.<br>
- First run now checks out images and theme.plists concurrently.<br>
- Code clean up and many refinements/improvements.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.57</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Revised checkout of theme.plists (thanks SoThOr). First run checks out all theme.plists and takes maybe a minute, but subsequent launches are far faster as previous data is used unless anything has changed.<br>
- Take note: All /&lt;mountpoint&gt;/EFI/Clover/themes paths are now set under version control.<br>
- Updates now work (for versioned theme directories only).<br>
- Updated html image links to use relative file paths.</p>
        </div>

        <div class="band1">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">v0.56</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- Themes are now listed alphabetically.<br>
- Added count of installed themes.<br>
- Installed themes are now highlighted by a different coloured band as opposed to a tick image.<br>
- Theme bands now filled with webkit grad rather than png image.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="band2">        
          <p class="textTitleSubHeading">Earlier versions</p>
          <p class="textSectionBody">- History lost when projectosx went down.</p>
        </div>
        
    </div>
    
    <!-- <div id="SpacerBottom">&nbsp;</div> -->

     
</div> <!-- End Container -->
    
</body>
</html>
            ]]>
            </description>
<!--INSERT_SPARKLE_UPDATE_DETAILS-->

        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>